# an array of question dictionaries
questions = [
    {
    "question": "How many members were in the group known as Monty Python?",
    "options": " four, three, eight, six ",
    "answer": "six"
},
{
    "question": "Who played the character of Arthur in the classic movie Monty Python and the Holy Grail?",
    "options": " Michael Palin, Graham Chapman, Eric Idle, Terry Jones ",
    "answer": "Graham Chapman"
},
{
    "question": "In the film Monty Python and the Holy Grail, how many questions does the Bridge Keeper ask?",
    "options": " three, one, none, four ",
    "answer": "three"
},
{
    "question": "WHich member of Monty Python appeared at the closing Olympic Ceremonies in London 2012?",
    "options": " Eric Idle, Terry Gilliam, Terry Jones, Michael Palin ",
    "answer": "Eric Idle"
},
{
    "question": "Which member of Monty Python died in 1989",
    "options": " Eric Idle, Terry Gilliam, Terry Jones, Michael Palin ",
    "answer": "Graham Chapman"
},
{
    "question": "When Monty Python needed funding, which famous rocker loaned them money?",
    "options": " George Harrison, Elton John, Eric Clapton, Rod Stewart ",
    "answer": "George Harrison"
},
{
    "question": "When did Monty Python's Flying Circus first air?",
    "options": " 1969, 1975, 1982, 1978",
    "answer": "1969"
},
{
    "question": "Which member of Monty Python created most of the sketches?",
    "options": " Terry Gilliam, Terry Jones, Eric Idle, Michael Palin ",
    "answer": "Terry Gilliam"
},
{
    "question": "Which member of Monty Python is the shortest?",
    "options": "  Eric Idle, Terry Jones, John Cleese, Terry Gilliam ",
    "answer": "Terry Jones"
},
{
    "question": "Eric Idle is the narrator on which of these films?",
    "options": " Ella Enchanted, Shawshank Redemption, The Princess Bride, The Thin Red Line ",
    "answer": "Ella Enchanted"
},
{
    "question": "When did the Meaning of Life Debut?",
    "options": "1983, 1976, 1972, 1986",
    "answer": "1983"
},
{
    "question": "Which member of Monty Python was responsible for Spamalot?",
    "options": "four, three, eight, six",
    "answer": "Eric Idle"
},
{
    "question": "Which North American network was the first to pick-up Monty Python's Flying Circus?",
    "options": "ABC, CBC, NBC, HBO",
    "answer": "CBC"
},
{
    "question": "Who plays Brian in The Life of Brian?",
    "options": " Eric Idle, Graham Chapman, John Cleese, Terry Gilliam ",
    "answer": "Graham Chapman"
},
{
    "question": "What was Brian's last name in the classic film The Life of Brian?",
    "options": "four, three, eight, six",
    "answer": "Cohen"
},
{
    "question": "Ireland banned the film The Life of Brian. What other nation did the same?",
    "options": "Germany, China, South America, Norway",
    "answer": "Norway"
},
{
    "question": "In Monty Python and the Holy Grail', what kind of shrubbery do the Knights Who Say Ni originally want?",
    "options": "a nice cheap one, a big wooden badger, a herring, a cat",
    "answer": "a nice cheap one"
},
{
    "question": "What happens to the Black Beast of Aaaarrgghhh in Monty Python's 'Monty Python and the Holy Grail'?",
    "options": " Sir Lancelot kills it, Snuffed By The Holy Hand Grenade, Head Is Bitten Off By Killer Rabbit, Animator Suffers A Heart Attack ",
    "answer": "Animator Suffers A Heart Attack"
},
{
    "question": "In Monty Python's 'Life of Brian', what was Brian's original occupation?",
    "options": " Selling Snacks At The Forum, He Didn't Have A Job, A Gladiator, A Carpenter",
    "answer": "Selling Snacks At The Forum"
},
{
    "question": "In 'Monty Python and the Holy Grail', what set off the Holy Hand Grenade of Antioch?",
    "options": "four, three, eight, six",
    "answer": "37623"
},
{
    "question": "What did the old man in 'Monty Python and the Holy Grail' ask when knights tried to cross a bridge?",
    "options": " Do You Like Cheese?, What Is Your Favorite Color?, How Old Are You?, What Is Your Name?",
    "answer": "What Is Your Name?"
},
{
    "question": "What was the name of the enchanter in 'Monty Python and the Holy Grail'?",
    "options": "He Didn't Have A Name, Brian, Arthur, Tim",
    "answer": "Tim"
},
{
    "question": "On which day does the lumberjack have buttered scones in Monty Python's 'The Lumberjack Song'?",
    "options": "Every Day, Wednesday, Thursday, Sunday",
    "answer": "Wednesday"
}
]
